我们希望FetchWeatherTask这个类返回代表天气预测结果的字符串队列
We want the FetchWeatherTask to return an array of string forecasts.
这意味着我们需要修正AsyncTask的返回类型
This means we need to modify the return type of the AsyncTask to be
为字符串数组
a string array.
这个的效果就是doInBackground方法将会返回
The effect of this is that the doInBackground method will now return
一个字符串数组
a string array.
在这个方法中  在我们查询了服务器以及
In this method, after we query the server and
读入流之后  我们将会执行这段代码
then read in the input stream, we're going to perform this code.
这段代码用来解析服务器的返回值  函数名为getWeatherDataFromJson
To parse the response from the server, we call getWeatherDataFromJson.
函数的输入为预测的JSON字符串  以及预测的天数
We pass in the forecast JSON string, as well as the number of forecast days.
为了确保返回的字符串数组的正确性
To make sure that this is returning the right string array,
我们可以在这个方法中 最后的位置 加入
we can go into the method, and then at the bottom of the method, we just add
一些日志 把字符串数组的每一个元素都打印出来
some logging statements to print out every element of the string array.
现在  当你编译这段代码并且在你的设备上运行的时候
Now, when you compile the code and run it on your device,
你可以点击刷新按钮从服务器中读取数据
you can hit the Refresh button to pull the data from the server.
然后  如果你打开日志栏  你就能看到这些数据被正确地解析
Then, if you open up log cat, you can see that it was parsed correctly,
你可以看到所有的预测条目都被打印在日志栏中
where you see all the forecast entries being printed out.